OBIDIKE, CHINEDU DAVID

Abuja, Nigeria | +2348091304672, +2347055972118 | chineduobidike92@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: www.linkedin.com/in/chinedu-obidike

SUMMARY

Empathetic and detail-oriented customer service professional with over 3 years of working experience. Demonstrated knowledge and experience in analysing customer complaints, developing corrective strategies, creating and implementing customer retention campaigns. Excellent communicator and listener with a knack for customer satisfaction, and keen organisational skills which allow for effective delivery of outstanding services. Able to juggle several tasks concurrently while always meeting all requirement and deadlines. Possess efficient and effective work ethic with highly improved leadership, relationship management, time management, and team working skills. Maintains the highest level of integrity; dedicated to providing reliable and friendly service without ever compromising the reputation of the organisation.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Y3 Distributions Nigeria Limited, Abuja.

2016 - Present

Customer Relations Officer/Administrative Support.

- Responsible for sales, customer acquisition, customer relationship management, & maximizing revenue.
- Liaising with other departments to ensure timely services are rendered to meet customer's expectation.
- Reviews written business requirements and technical specifications.
- Creates unit test plans, scripts, test harnesses and investigate reported defects.
- Provides support and trains people to ensure the CRM is understood by new and existing users and helps the system to grow and evolve.
- Attends regular meetings with support staff and team members to review upcoming issues, items, and training.
- Increased customer satisfaction rate from 72% to 93% by responding quickly to customer needs and developing relationships with the customer.
- Ensures accurate data input and maintenance of client information in CRM system.

A+ Tutors, Asaba, Delta State.

2015 - 2016

Teacher

- Assessed development of students and modified teaching style to accommodate different learning needs.
- Administered a standardized test and identified different instructional resources and methods to meet students' varying learning needs.
- Observed and evaluated student's performance and development.
- Collaborated with the management and parents on academic intervention and support programs for students.

Zappa Mixed Secondary School, Asaba, Delta State

2015 - 2016

Teaching Assistant

- Provided guidance and advice to students on educational and social matters and on their further education and future careers.
- Observed and evaluated student's performance and development.
- Collaborated with the management and parents when various students needed academic intervention or support programs.
- Supervised and coordinated the Students during school hours.

National Institute of Pharmaceutical Research and Development, Abuja. 2013

Laboratory Assistant

- Operated and calibrated laboratory scales, analytical, and other support equipment as needed.
- Performed work under strict SOP's and government operating procedures.
- Assisted in general maintenance and upkeep of the lab including maintenance of the supplies.
- Performed and Participated in all phases of research including planning, preparation, calibration, application, evaluation, data analysis, maintenance and when necessary, appropriate disposal.
- Reported sound scientific conclusions based on data analysis, with the result and conclusions, generated impacting research plans and advancement decisions on the experimental materials.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Stand-in-President, St. Anthony of Padua, St. Peter Clavar Catholic Chaplaincy, University of Abuja.
 2012 - 2014

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

- IBM Applied Artificial Intelligence Specialization
 2020
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing, Google Digital Garage
 2018
- Basic First Aid/CPR, Novelle-Center Training Institute.
 2016
- Fire Safety and Risk Assessment, Department of Petroleum Resources
 2016
- Health Safety and Environment; HSE 1,2,3, British International Safety Organization (BISO)
 2015

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Chemistry
 University of Abuja, FCT.

2014

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- Excellent and articulate verbal and written communicator.
- Customer Orientation.
- Organisational Awareness.
- Influencing and Negotiation Skills.
- Adaptability and Flexibility.
- Customer Relationship Management.
- Reporting and Documentation.
- Managing and Organising Information.

- Web Development; HTML & CSS
- Creative Writing.
- Analytical Skills.
- Strong Work Ethics.
- Independent Thinker.
- Research and Experimentation.
- Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite.
- Interpersonal & Communication Skills.

 Ability to Multitask and Effective Time Management